uncubed.com 2019-03-06

# Privacy Policy | Uncubed

Uncubed (Parrut, Inc. and our affiliates) is committed to protecting your privacy and giving you a clear understanding of how we use information, including your personal information, and what rights and controls you have. This Privacy Policy governs the use of information on Uncubed.com and any other website we own and operate (together, the “Websites”). If you do not agree with this policy, we recommend not using our website or our services. 

We will periodically make updates to this policy. When we do so, we will endeavor to make you aware of those changes through email notifications, blog posts, and other communications. Still, we encourage you to periodically review this policy. 

## Information We Collect From You

You can use our Websites without providing any personal information. When you register for a user account, we ask you for Personal Information (defined below), in order to deliver an effective, efficient experience and service. 

## Personal Information

This is any information that you voluntarily submit to us that personally identifies you. This can include name, email address, company name, address, phone number, payment information, or other information about you. 

Personal information can include information that you submit directly to our website, or information that is available on the internet, such as from LinkedIn, Facebook, Google, or other service providers (collectively, “Personal Information”). 

## Information We Collect From Third Parties

Occasionally, we may receive information about you from third party sources including partners with whom we offer co-branded services or marketing promotions, and other publicly available sources such as social media services. In such cases, we will confirm our understanding that you have opted into those services or promotions. 

## Log Files

When you use our services or view our content, our system automatically collects information about your computer or device hardware and software. This can include information about your browser, ISP, operating system, access time, and content or files viewed on our site. We may link this data to Personal Information. This information is used by Uncubed to improve and better understand usage of the Websites, including the gathering of general statistics by users, and to deliver a better experience to you. 

## Cookies & Other Similar Technology

Uncubed uses cookies, beacons, or similar technology on the Websites to facilitate the most effective user experience, analyze trends, and generally collect information about how our users are are interacting with the Websites and services. 

You can set your web browser to refuse cookies. You will still be permitted to use the Websites if you do so, although some portions of the Websites, and some functionality, may be restricted or reduced. 

## How We Use Information We Collect 

Use of Personal Information 

As noted elsewhere in the Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information for one or more of the following applications: 

  * To improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Websites and other parts of the service, including job recommendations and content delivery. 
  * To promote relevant Uncubed services or features to you, in conjunction with the communication preferences that you have selected for your account. 
  * To provide select summary information to partners and other third parties, none of which will identify. 
  * To distribute other information to you, including changes in our terms of service, this Privacy Policy, or other legal agreements. 
  * To meet any legal requirements that Uncubed is subject to. 

We also collect navigational information about your computer or other devices including IP address, geographical information, browser used, and activity during visits. This information is collected in order to better understand our general community of users, to enable third party analytics providers including Google Analytics, and to deliver an efficient, customized, and valuable user experience. 

Privacy Policy Compliance 

The information we collect is only used in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. All customers and users are obligated to comply with this Privacy Policy. 

We Will Not Sell Personal Information 

Uncubed will not sell your Personal Information to another party. 

Customer Testimonials 

We may post customer or user testimonials on our Websites. We obtain consent prior to posting. 

Use of Credit Card Information 

We use third-party, PCI-compliant services to process all credit card payments. These providers are not permitted to store information you provide, except where you direct them to do so, should they provide that option. 

Security and Storage of Personal Information 

We utilize a number of internal and third-party storage and security procedures for Personal Information. This data is secured on third-party servers in a controlled, secure environment, and protected from unauthorized access or use. We also work to regularly review the policies of our third party service providers for their storage and security protocols. 

Retention of Personal Information 

We retain Personal Information for as long as we have an ongoing legitimate business purpose to keep it. This includes as long as is required to contact you about your account or Uncubed’s services, to comply and audit opt-out requests, and as needed to satisfy legal obligations, to resolve our disputes, and otherwise enforce our agreements. 

After this period, we will delete Personal Information, anonymize it, or otherwise securely store it securely until deletion is possible. We will delete this information from our servers at an earlier date if specifically requested by you. 

If you provide Personal Information to an Uncubed customer or partner through our Websites or other service, that information will be subject to their policies and procedures. 

After termination of an account, we may delete all customer information and Personal Information, unless retention is legally required. 

If you are registered to receive our marketing communications, we retain your information for a reasonable time period after the last indication of interest in our content and services, including opening an email from us, logging into your Uncubed account, or otherwise interacting with the Websites. 

External Websites 

Uncubed Websites may provide links to other websites. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these websites. 

## How to Access, Control, and Delete Your Personal Information

You can unsubscribe from our non-transactional email and marketing communications through the “Unsubscribe” link on the bottom of our emails, by updating the preferences associated with your account on the Websites, or by requesting changes. Transactional emails are those delivered to confirm changes in preferences or those used to announce changes to our policies and terms. 

We are not responsible for, nor can we manage, any Personal Information you have provided to our customers or partners. To access, control, or otherwise manage your information with 3rd parties other than Uncubed and the Websites, you should contact those parties directly. 

In addition to the opportunity to unsubscribe and otherwise manage your account directly on the Websites, you have the following data protection rights: (i) you can request access, updates to, or deletion of your Personal Information, (ii) you can withdraw your consent for us to collect and process your Personal Information at any time (noting that this will not affect the legality of any information processed prior to the withdrawal of your consent), and (iii) you can complain to the relevant data protection authority about our use of your Personal Information. 

## How to Contact Uncubed 

Mailing Address 

50 Eldridge Street, 5th Floor  
New York, NY 10002 

Email Address
